<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LightApp</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text"></string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="start_plugin">Start with the plug-in principle</string>
    <string name="resources_intro_title">About @Resources</string>
    <string name="resources_intro">Class for accessing an application&#x27;s resources. This sits on top of the asset manager of the application (accessible through getAssets()) and provides a high-level API for getting typed data from the assets.

The Android resource system keeps track of all non-code assets associated with an application. You can use this class to access your application&#x27;s resources. You can generally acquire the Resources instance associated with your application with getResources().

The Android SDK tools compile your application&#x27;s resources into the application binary at build time. To use a resource, you must install it correctly in the source tree (inside your project&#x27;s res/ directory) and build your application. As part of the build process, the SDK tools generate symbols for each resource, which you can use in your application code to access the resources.

Using application resources makes it easy to update various characteristics of your application without modifying code, and—by providing sets of alternative resources—enables you to optimize your application for a variety of device configurations (such as for different languages and screen sizes). This is an important aspect of developing Android applications that are compatible on different types of devices.</string>
    <string name="title_item_list">Items</string>
    <string name="title_item_detail">Item Detail</string>
    <string name="with_flutter">Compare Flutter</string>
</resources>
